<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.7" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.7" modifiedDate="2025-10-27T19:18:55">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Praise (Live)</title>
      <title>Praise (Live) (feat. Brandon Lake, Chris Brown &amp; Chandler Moore)</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Elevation Worship</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="i1">
      <lines>Let everything that has breath<br/>Praise the Lord (You got it), praise the Lord<br/><p style="page-break-after: always;"/><br/>Let everything, let everything that has breath<br/>Praise the Lord, praise the Lord<br/><p style="page-break-after: always;"/><br/>(Let everything) Let everything (Hey) that has breath (Hey)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines break="optional">I'll praise in the valley, praise on the mountain (Yeah)<br/>I'll praise when I'm sure, praise when I'm doubting</lines>
      <lines>I'll praise when outnumbered, praise when surrounded<br/>'Cause praise is the waters my enemies drown in</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>As long as I'm breathing<br/>I've got a reason to<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul (C'mon)<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>I'll praise when I feel it, and I'll praise when I don't (Yeah)<br/>I'll praise 'cause I know You're still in control<br/>'Cause my praise is a weapon, it's more than a sound (More than a sound)<br/>Oh, my praise is the shout that brings Jericho down (Yeah)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c2">
      <lines break="optional">As long as I'm breathing<br/>I've got a reason to<br/>Praise the Lord (C'mon), oh my soul<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul</lines>
      <lines>I won't be quiet, my God is alive<br/>So how could I keep it inside? (I gotta)<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul<br/>(Yeah, praise the Lord)</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="o1">
      <lines>C'mon, let me see that dance, put a dance on it tonight (Yeah)<br/>If you're grateful, c'mon<br/>Hey, hey, yeah</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="b1">
      <lines break="optional">I'll praise 'cause You're sovereign, praise 'cause You reign<br/>Praise 'cause You rose and defeated the grave<br/>I'll praise 'cause You're faithful, praise 'cause You're true<br/>Praise 'cause there's nobody greater than You</lines>
      <lines>I'll praise 'cause You're sovereign, praise 'cause You reign (You reign)<br/>Praise 'cause You rose and defeated the grave<br/>I'll praise 'cause You're faithful, praise 'cause You're true<br/>Praise 'cause there's nobody greater than You</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c3">
      <lines>Praise the Lord, oh my soul<br/>(C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon)<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul (Praise the Lord, oh my soul)<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul<br/><p style="page-break-after: always;"/><br/>I won't be quiet, my God is alive<br/>How could I keep it inside? (How could I)<br/>I won't be quiet, my God is alive<br/>How could I keep it inside? (I won't keep quiet)<br/>I won't be quiet, my God is alive<br/>How could I keep it inside? (I gotta)<br/>Praise the Lord, oh my soul</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="e1">
      <lines>Jump, jump, jump, jump<br/>Let everything that has breath (Hey, hey)<br/>Praise the Lord (Hey, hey), praise the Lord<br/>Let everything, let everything that has breath<br/><p style="page-break-after: always;"/><br/>(C'mon, c'mon, c'mon)<br/>Praise the Lord (C'mon, c'mon)<br/>Praise the Lord (C'mon, c'mon)<br/>(Let everything), Let everything that has breath<br/>Praise the Lord, praise the Lord, praise the Lord<br/><p style="page-break-after: always;"/><br/>(Let everything), Let everything that has breath<br/>(Praise the Lord)<br/>Praise the Lord, praise the Lord, praise the Lord</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
